Guide to the Serpent's Tail/High Risk Archives ca. 1990-1997 MSS 86 MSS 086
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
Serpent's Tail/High Risk Archive
ca. 1990-1997
MSS 086
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
39.0 linear feet (27 boxes)
High Risk Books was founded in New York City in 1993 by Ira Silverberg and Amy Scholder as an imprint of Serpent's Tail Press in London. Dedicated to publishing challenging, innovative, and progressive literature, High Risk Books transcended the traditional boundaries of publishing to provoke and inspire a new generation of writers and readers. While connected by a certain subversive impulse, authors as diverse as William S. Burroughs, Kathy Acker, Tim Dlugos, Diamanda Galas, Robert Gluck, Gary Indiana, June Jordan, Cookie Mueller, Lynne Tillman, Pagan Kennedy, John Giorno, Sapphire and many others are published by High Risk. As a small press, High Risk played a crucial role in providing a space for writers, many just beginning their careers, who would otherwise have found it difficult to get published in mainstream houses. In January 1997, the High Risk office in New York closed. Serpent's Tail Press continues to publish from the United Kingdom.
High Risk Books (Firm).
Provenance
The Serpent's Tail/High Risk Archive was donated February, 1997 by Ira Silverberg. The initial organization of the collection was done by High Risk staff as they packed the materials for shipment.
Access Restrictions
Open to researchers. Appointments are necessary for the use of manuscript and archival materials.
Historical Note
High Risk Books was founded in New York City in 1993 by Ira Silverberg and Amy Scholder as an imprint of Serpent's Tail Press in London. Dedicated to publishing challenging, innovative, and progressive literature, High Risk Books transcended the traditional boundaries of publishing to provoke and inspire a new generation of writers and readers. Ira Silverberg told The New York Times in a March 13, 1994 interview that he and his co-editor Amy Scholder wanted to "catch an area of the market that's being overlooked by mainstream houses.... We're working with a lot of gay men, lesbians, and African Americans, because the voices of under served communities tend to shed more light on societal conditions than the voices of the people who have the franchise. That's not to say we won't publish straight white men." While connected by a certain subversive impulse, authors as diverse as William S. Burroughs, Kathy Acker, Tim Dlugos, Diamanda Galas, Robert Gluck, Gary Indiana, June Jordan, Cookie Mueller, Lynne Tillman, Pagan Kennedy, John Giorno, Sapphire and many others are published by High Risk.
As a small press High Risk played a crucial role in providing a space for writers, many just beginning their careers, who would otherwise have found it difficult to get published in mainstream houses. Anny Patty, editor-at-large at Crown Publishing, complimented Ira Silverberg for "publishing a kind of book that's very hard for corporate publishers to get past committees, which tend to homogenize things. He's able to publish non-homogenized writing and to sort out those who are posing from those who really have something to say." Ira's larger agenda for High Risk Books can be summed up in his statement to The New York Times: "I hope we'll be seen as the diamond in the coal bin that publishing is right now. I want to prove to the world that literary publishing has a future".
In January, 1997, the High Risk office in New York closed. Serpent's Tail Press continues to publish from the United Kingdom.
Scope and Content Note
The Serpent's Tail/High Risk Archive is a part of the Downtown Collection at the Fales Library, New York University. The Fales Library is the primary special collections division of the NYU libraries, housing over 167,000 volumes of English and American literature from 1700 to the present. Strengths of the collection include the development of the English and American novel, with an emphasis on the Gothic and the Victorian novel. The Downtown Collection, of which the High Risk Archive is a part, is a comprehensive collection of author and business files, printed materials, manuscripts, photographs and other materials related to the Downtown New York scene from ca. 1975 to the present.
The archival portion of the Serpent's Tail/High Risk Archive is comprised of the correspondence, manuscripts and contracts of authors who published with High Risk Books, press binders on High Risk and Serpent's Tail authors, business and administration files, production files, publicity, reviews, photographs, sales catalogues, posters, ephemera, and some audio/visual and printed material. The Serpent's Tail/High Risk Archive contains a comprehensive collection of High Risk Books files during the years of its operation. Ira Silverberg's original organization of the archive was preserved as much as possible.
Series I (Author files) subseries A contains four boxes of High Risk author files. This subseries is arranged alphabetically by author and includes information on appearances and events, contracts, royalty and sub-rights, correspondence, author data, production, publicity, and reviews. Series I, subseries B contains three boxes of Serpent's Tail author files, arranged by author and further subdivided by title. Also included are authors/titles published collaboratively by both Atlas Press and Serpent's Tail.
Series II (Business and administrative files): Contains five boxes of editorial and general correspondence, as well as correspondence with the U.K. office, Atlas Press, and Consortium Book Sales and Distribution. It also includes business files pertaining to customer accounts, advertising, events, trade shows, the High Risk website, marketing research, academic and review requests, publication schedules, permissions, and budgets.
Series III (Manuscripts): Contains five boxes of manuscripts found scattered throughout the collection. This series also includes versions of texts that reflect the various stages of production (from manuscript to advance uncorrected proof).
Series IV (Production files): Contains two boxes of production materials, sometimes with manuscripts. All galleys were removed and catalogued for the Fales Downtown Collection.
Series V (Publicity and Promotion), subseries A contains three boxes of promotional materials, sales kits, and material removed from press binders and put in folders for the collection. Series V, subseries B contains author photographs and slides of authors and cover art. Series 5 subseries C contains sales catalogues from High Risk, Serpent's Tail, and Consortium Book Sales and Distribution.
Series VI (Miscellaneous), subseries A contains subject files on Paul Miller, a.k.a. DJ Spooky, and Richard Tremblay, a.k.a. Rick Trembles. Series VI, subseries B contains printed material. Series 6 subseries C contains ephemera. Series 6 subseries D contains computer disks from the High Risk office.
Accretion 2011 - Series VII (Cookie Mueller Material): contains manuscripts, newspaper and magazine publications, and drafts of Cookie Mueller's writings. It also contains personal photographs, drawings, and other materials belonging to Cookie Mueller.
Flat: There is one flat oversize box that contain oversize materials from series 1, 5 and 6. Posters of William Burroughs from series I are located in the map case.
Arrangement
Folders are arranged alphabetically by name/subject within each series. Oversize materials are separated into their own container.
The files are grouped into six subject oriented series.
Series I: Author Files
Series II: Business and Administrative Files
Series III: Manuscripts
Series IV: Production Files
Series V: Publicity, Photographs and Sales Catalogs
Series VI: Miscellaneous
Accretion 2011 - Series VII: Cookie Mueller Materials
Flat Box - Series I: Author Files
Flat Box - Series V: Publicity, Photographs and Sales Catalogs
Flat Box - Series VI: Miscellaneous
Related Material at the Fales Library and Special Collections
Between C and D Archive
Tim Dlugos Papers
The Dennis Cooper Papers
The David Wojnarowicz Papers
Separated Material
There is no information about materials that are associated by provenance to the described materials that have been physically separated or removed.
Acker, Kathy, 1948-1997; Atlas Press (Firm).; Burroughs, William S., 1914-1997; Dlugos, Tim; Gal, Diama; Giorno, John; Glück, Robert; High Risk Books (Firm).; Indiana, Gary; Jordan, June, 1936-2002; Kennedy, Pagan, 1962-; Mueller, Cookie; Sapphire, 1950-; Serpent’s Tail (Firm).; Silverberg, Ira; Tillman, Lynne; Authors, American |y 20th century.; Business records.; Contracts.; Correspondence.; Ephemera.; Literature, Experimental.; Literature, Modern |y 20th century.; Manuscripts for publication.; New York (N.Y.); New York (N.Y.) |x Intellectual life |y 20th century.; Photographs.; Poets, American |y 20th century.; Press kits.; Reviews (document genre); Sales catalogs.; Scripts (documents); Small presses |z New York (State) |z New York.
- Series I: Author Files
  - Subseries A: High Risk author files
    - Acker, Kathy--contract, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Acker, Kathy--correspondence, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Acker, Kathy--data, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Acker, Kathy--production, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Acker, Kathy--reviews, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Bornstein / Sullivan--contract, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Bornstein / Sullivan--correspondence, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Bornstein / Sullivan--data, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Bornstein / Sullivan--production, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Bornstein / Sullivan--publicity, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Bornstein / Sullivan--reviews, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Burroughs, William--contract, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Burroughs, William--correspondence, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Burroughs, William--data, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Burroughs, William--production, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Burroughs, William--publicity, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Burroughs, William--posters (see folder in map case), undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 16a)
    - Burroughs, William--reviews, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Burroughs, William--royalties / subrights, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Bush, Catherine--contract, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Bush, Catherine--correspondence, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Bush, Catherine--data, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Bush, Catherine--production, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Bush, Catherine--publicity, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Bush, Catherine--reviews, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Bush, Catherine--royalties / subrights, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Camus, Renaud--contract, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Camus, Renaud--correspondence, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Camus, Renaud--data, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Camus, Renaud--production, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Camus, Renaud--publicity, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Camus, Renaud--reviews, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Camus, Renaud--royalties / subrights, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Carter, Charlotte--contract, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Carter, Charlotte--correspondence, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Cortez, Jayne--contract, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Cortez, Jayne--correspondence, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Cortez, Jayne--data, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Cortez, Jayne--production, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Cortez, Jayne--publicity, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Cortez, Jayne--reviews, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Davis, Lydia--contract, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Davis, Lydia--correspondence, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Davis, Lydia--data, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Davis, Lydia--production, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Davis, Lydia--publicity, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Davis, Lydia--reviews, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Dlugos, Tim--contract, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Dlugos, Tim--correspondence, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Dlugos, Tim--data, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Dlugos, Tim--production, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Dlugos, Tim--publicity, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Dlugos, Tim--reviews, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Galas, Diamanda--contract, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Galas, Diamanda--correspondence, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Galas, Diamanda--data, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Galas, Diamanda--misc (see flat box), undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 55a)
    - Galas, Diamanda--production, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Galas, Diamanda--publicity, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Gilroy, Paul--correspondence, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Gilroy, Paul--reviews, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Giorno, John--appearance / events, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Giorno, John--contract, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Giorno, John--correspondence, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Giorno, John--data, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Giorno, John--production, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Giorno, John--publicity, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Giorno, John--reviews, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Giorno, John--royalties / subrights, undated; 31142040616966 (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Glück, Robert--appearances / events, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Glück, Robert--contract, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Glück, Robert--correspondence, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Glück, Robert--data, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Glück, Robert--production, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Glück, Robert--publicity, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Glück, Robert--reviews, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Glück, Robert--royalties / subrights, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Goodis, David--contract, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Goodis, David--correspondence, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Goodis, David--data, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Guibert, Herve. contract, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Guibert, Herve. correspondence, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Guibert, Herve. data, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Guibert, Herve. production, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Guibert, Herve. publicity, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Guibert, Herve. reviews, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Guibert, Herve. royalties / subrights, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Home, Stewart--production, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - Home, Stewart--publicity, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Home, Stewart--reviews, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - House, Richard--contract, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - House, Richard--correspondence, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - House, Richard--data, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - Indiana, Gary--appearances / events, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - Indiana, Gary--contracts, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - Indiana, Gary--correspondence, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - Indiana, Gary--data, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - Indiana, Gary--production, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - Indiana, Gary--publicity, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - Indiana, Gary--reviews, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - Indiana, Gary--royalties / subrights, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - Johnston, Jill--contract, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - Johnston, Jill--reviews, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - Jordan, June--appearances / events, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - Jordan, June--contract, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 103)
    - Jordan, June--correspondence, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 104)
    - Jordan, June--data, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 105)
    - Jordan, June--production, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 106)
    - Jordan, June--publicity, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 107)
    - Jordan, June--reviews, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 108)
    - Jordan, June--royalties / subrights, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 109)
    - Kennedy, Pagan--appearances / events, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 110)
    - Kennedy, Pagan--contracts, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 111)
    - Kennedy, Pagan--correspondence, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 112)
    - Kennedy, Pagan--data, undated; 31142040616974 (Box 2, Folder 113)
    - Kennedy, Pagan--production, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - Kennedy, Pagan--publicity, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - Kennedy, Pagan--reviews, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - Kennedy, Pagan--royalties / subrights, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - Kertess, Klaus--contract, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - Kertess, Klaus--correspondence, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - Kertess, Klaus--data, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 120)
    - Kertess, Klaus--production, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 121)
    - Klein, Adam--appearances / events, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 122)
    - Klein, Adam--contract, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - Klein, Adam--correspondence, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - Klein, Adam--data, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - Klein, Adam--production, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 126)
    - Klein, Adam--publicity, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - Klein, Adam--reviews, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 128)
    - Klein, Adam--royalties / subrights, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 129)
    - Lambert, Gavin--contract, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 130)
    - Lambert, Gavin--correspondence, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 131)
    - Lambert, Gavin--data, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 132)
    - Lambert, Gavin--production, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 133)
    - Lambert, Gavin--publicity, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 134)
    - Levin, Ira--data, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 135)
    - Levin, Ira--production, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 136)
    - Levin, Ira--publicity, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 137)
    - Lewis, Heather--contract, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 138)
    - Lewis, Heather--correspondence, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 139)
    - Lewis, Heather--data, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 140)
    - Lewis, Heather--production, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 141)
    - Lewis, Heather--publicity, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 142)
    - Lewis, Heather--reviews, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 143)
    - Lewis, Heather--royalties / subrights, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 144)
    - McCoy, Horace--contract, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 145)
    - McCoy, Horace--correspondence, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 146)
    - McCoy, Horace--data, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 147)
    - McCoy, Horace--production, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 148)
    - McCoy, Horace--publicity, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 149)
    - McCoy, Horace--royalties, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 150)
    - Meer, Ameena--appearances / events, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 151)
    - Meer, Ameena--contract, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 152)
    - Meer, Ameena--correspondence, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 153)
    - Meer, Ameena--data, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 154)
    - Meer, Ameena--production, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 155)
    - Meer, Ameena--publicity, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 156)
    - Meer, Ameena--reviews, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 157)
    - Meer, Ameena--royalties / subrights, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 158)
    - Meyer, Stewart--contract, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 159)
    - Meyer, Stewart--correspondence, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 160)
    - Meyer, Stewart--data, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 161)
    - Meyer, Stewart--production, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 162)
    - Meyer, Stewart--publicity, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 163)
    - Meyer, Stewart--reviews, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 164)
    - Misc. authors, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 165)
    - Mueller, Cookie--contract, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 166)
    - Mueller, Cookie--correspondence, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 167)
    - Mueller, Cookie--data, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 168)
    - Mueller, Cookie--production, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 169)
    - Mueller, Cookie--publicity, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 170)
    - Olson, Jenni--appearances / events, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 171)
    - Olson, Jenni--contract, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 172)
    - Olson, Jenni--correspondence, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 173)
    - Olson, Jenni--data, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 174)
    - Olson, Jenni--production, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 175)
    - Olson, Jenni--publicity, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 176)
    - Olson, Jenni--reviews, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 177)
    - Peabody, Richard--contract, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 178)
    - Peabody, Richard--correspondence, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 179)
    - Peabody, Richard--data, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 180)
    - Peabody, Richard--production, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 181)
    - Peabody, Richard--publicity, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 182)
    - Pelecanos, George--contract, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 183)
    - Pelecanos, George--correspondence, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 184)
    - Purdy, James--contract, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 185)
    - Purdy, James--correspondence, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 186)
    - Purdy, James--data, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 187)
    - Purdy, James--reviews, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 188)
    - Purdy, James--royalties / subrights, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 189)
    - Rower, Ann--contract, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 190)